Haroon Badshah

Web Developer

Personal details



Haroon Badshah



larvaweb999@gmail.com



+923156699964



Nowshehra



Male



Pakistan



linkedin.com/in/haroon-badshah-902b2a1

Skills

PHP

Laravel

JavaScript

JQuery

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

Ajax

Strapi

Livewire

Codeigniter

WordPress

Photoshop

Googling

VUE JS

Profile

Experienced Developer with over 3 years of experience in PHP|Laravel. Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction.

Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.

Education

BS(Computer Science)

The University of Agricultural

Feb 2015 - Aug 2018

Employment

Web Developer

Jun 2021 - Present

Seven Koncepts, Rawalpindi

- Conducted research, gathered information from multiple sources and presented results.
- Drove operational improvements which resulted in savings and improved profit margins.
- Worked to maintain outstanding attendance record, consistently arriving to work ready to start immediately.
- Identified issues, analyzed information and provided solutions to problems.
- Maintained excellent attendance record, consistently arriving to work on time.
- Developed and implemented performance improvement strategies and plans to promote continuous improvement.
- · Exceeded goals through effective task prioritization and great work ethic.
- Developed and maintained courteous and effective working relationships.
- Created plans and communicated deadlines to complete projects on time.

Laravel Devloper

Aug 2020 - Jun 2021

RedStonz, Peshawar

- Developed and maintained courteous and effective working relationships.
- Created plans and communicated deadlines to complete projects on time.
- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions.
- Increased customer satisfaction by resolving issues.
- Learned new skills and applied to daily tasks to improve efficiency and productivity.
- Participated in team-building activities to enhance working relationships.
- Collaborated with team members to achieve target results.
- Worked flexible hours across night, weekend and holiday shifts.

Languages

English

Urdu

Pashto